Cut it out already! I've already told you everything I know!
I'm sorry, but we're under Lt. Col. Archer's orders.
Don't give me that!
I'm in a hurry here!
Welcome, Crimson Alchemist, Zolf J. Kimbly.
As well as the Sewing Life Alchemist, Shou Tucker.
I've kept my end of the promise.
Now for you...
I know.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I will secure your safety,
or my name isn't Frank Archer.
M-My safety?
That's right. You are going to return to the military
and continue your research, directly beneath me.
I can continue my research?
Yes.
Change of mission directives.
Show no mercy to anyone who opposes us.
Eliminate any troublemakers who are infesting this bar.
B-But are you sure we should?
I don't care.
As long as I have Tucker,
I can make as many of those
sorts of guys as I want to, after all.
And Greed can't lay a hand on me
as long as I have this.
Man cannot obtain anything
without first sacrificing something.
In order to obtain anything,
something of equal value is required.
That is alchemy's
Law of Equivalent Exchange.
At the time, we believed that
to be the true way of the world.
Dammit...
Those bastards!
Greed-san, this way!
Wh-What?!
My name is Alex Louis Armstrong.
People call me
the Strong Arm Alchemist.
Major!
You will return...
Alphonse Elric to me.
My word...
Sloth sure is a slave driver.
Then again, she was responsible for letting him escape,
so I guess she has no choice.
So, what will you do, Greed?
You see that?
That is the artistic alchemy that has been passed down
among the Armstrong family for generations.
You look like you're going to be a tough customer.
I'm going to have to
mean business.
How bizarre...
It has been some time since my blood boiled and my muscles danced.
Impressive, Armstrong.
Your arms are as strong as ever.
I also participated in the battle to exterminate Ishbal, as a grunt.
You're a former comrade?
In that case, I have even less desire to take your life needlessly.
Surrender!
That is too much to ask.
Major! Please stand aside!
Major!
Do not throw your lives away!
Yeah, we're not going to.
What?
Tell Kimbly and Tucker for me...
that I will be sure
to return the favor.
He sure is quiet,
especially considering
how loud he was earlier.
He must have grown
tired of carrying on.
I'm glad he has, myself.
Yeah, I guess so.
So we're the only ones
who got away, huh?
Damn!
Well then, what do I do now?
How long do you intend to keep running away?
I think it might be
too late for you.
You...
You've already seen
Gluttony here, haven't you?
Pleased to meet you.
I'm the current Lust.
You?
To cut to the chase, Greed,
you've come to
a fork in the road.
You can be sealed up again,
or you can be destroyed right here.
You think I can be
done in by you?
Have you forgotten?
You, a homunculus,
were sealed up by a certain someone
after rebelling 140 years ago.
That person is angry.
It's about time we brought this to an end, Greed.
An end! An end!
Sorry about this, boy,
but you'll have to help us.
Take care of Martel.
Roa-san... Dolcetto-san...
H-Hold on, what's happening?!
Please go, Greed-san.
We'll take care of this.
Guys...
We can't afford
to lose you here.
We'll leave it to you
to avenge us all.
You sure are keeping some loyal pawns, aren't you?
I've been merged
together with a dog,
and dogs have a strong
sense of loyalty.
You cannot go beyond this point!
Greed-san!
Come on!
It's no use running.
You can tuck tail
and run too, Dolcetto.
I'd like to do just that,
but these guys
took a shot at me.
You're sure?
Too late to back out now.
Is that...
That's where
Dante-san's house is!
For crying out loud,
you sure are sociable.
You had the chance to run
in the midst of all that trouble.
That's easy for you to say.
No matter. Hey, Martel...
Yes?
Stay inside there until morning.
If I'm not back by then,
you get away by yourself. Got it?
Greed-san!
What are you planning to do?
Sorry about this, boy.
That's how it is.
U-Uh...
Let me out!
Open up, I tell you!
You can't! Greed-san
said not to come out!
Shut up!
So I wound up
coming back here after all...
I wonder why my legs
brought me here.
Do they want me to
beg her for my life?
Or something else?
That's a good boy, Greed.
This is just as you-know-who thought it would unfold.
We're done?
Yes. Our job is done here.
I'm hungry.
Who are you?
The reason you came here...
is because this is your birthplace.
Why, you...
Are those...
They're your bones.
Who are you?
What did Dante tell you?
If it's Dante-sama you want,
she's over there.
What's going on here?
It can't be...!
There's no way a kid like you can do something like this!
Who the hell is behind this?!
It couldn't be...!
Is that...
My...
My life!
Dammit...
I've found you, Greed!
Dante-san?!
Greed!
What the hell did you do?!
Good question.
I'd like to know, myself.
Are you the one
who killed her?
How about it?!
Well, makes no difference to me if you think so.
Why would you do
something like this?
Why have you come this far
to save your brother?
Al is my brother!
You're ready for this, are you?
Where is Al? Give him the hell
back to me right now!
If you want me to return him,
then you know what to do.
Let me out!
I can't!
What's the matter?
Is that all the resolve
you've got?
Correct me.
I'm an error, aren't I?
I told you before, didn't I?
If you want to defeat me...
...then fight with the intent to kill you, right?
That's right.
That's my mechanic for you.
Even like this, I can still move it.
Let's go!
That didn't hurt one bit, kid.
This time, it's... my turn!
Wh-What the hell
did you do to my shield?!
If you think about it,
it's pretty simple.
You can't create something
out of nothing.
In other words, you've got to be fashioning that shield thing of yours from someplace.
Even though you're a homunculus,
they say that the components of your body
are still the same, don't they?
The substance within
your body's composition
that can be converted into
a very hard, durable material...
It's what comprises
a third of your body: carbon.
The hardness changes depending on
how the carbon atoms have been arranged.
From pencil leads
all the way up to diamonds.
Once I know the structure,
the rest is right up my alley!
Where is Al?
I haven't lost yet...
This fight is over, isn't it?
You heard from your brother, right?
I don't die all that easily.
Then I'll just have to hammer you until you decide you want to talk.
That's it! It wouldn't be fun
any other way.
There's the kid I was hoping for.
Bring it on!
Here goes!
Nicely... done...
Where's Al?
Where did you take Al?!
I let him go
a long time ago.
Greed?
Homunculi...
are born when you alchemists
perform human transmutations.
When we are...
brought before the bones of the person they attempted to bring back to life,
we aren't able to move freely.
That is the homunculi's
Achilles' heel.
Why? Why are you
telling me this?
Knowing you,
you can defeat them.
I can't bear to let myself be sealed up again.
Greed... are you...
I am avarice, after all.
I will do with my life as I like.
Greed!
Defeat... them...
I'm counting... on you...
H-Hey... you're kidding, right?
Greed! Hey!
What are you doing?!
Are you screwing with me?!
I thought I could knock your head off
and you wouldn't die!
Hey! Greed!
What is this?
Martel-san...
Um...
Did my teacher say anything?
No. By the time I got here, she was already gone.
I don't know where
Lyra went off to, either.
Sensei, I really am
sorry about this.
We're going to Ishbal.
If we stayed by your side any longer, Sensei, we'd just be in your way.
Sensei, there's a possibility
that the military is after you,
so could I ask you to go into hiding for a little while?
Of all the... If it's come to me being worried over by you, then it's all over.
You're going,
no matter what I say?
Yes.
No matter what happens,
we will continue our journey
until we get our own bodies back.
I'll see you later.
Right.
Fullmetal Alchemist...
Episode 35: "Fool's Reunion"
Where do we come from, and where are we going?
Are those the questions of a fool?